# **Eva Walls**

Indianapolis, Indiana 46217 https://www.linkedin.com/in/eva-walls 317-507-3845 EvaWalls@gmail.com

# **Email and Jr. Web Developer**

Using tools and experience, complete projects and tasks meeting committed deadlines. Support marketing and communications projects for clients in information technology, associate relations, corporate sales, product owners, and senior management. Identify and implement needed enhancements to websites, portals and email campaigns. Technical resource for development of advanced email communications.

# **Professional Experience**

Anthem, Inc.

June 2017 - March 2020

## **Digital Content Operations Manager**

June 2017 - March 2020

Served as subject matter expert to clients and creative team/agencies for best practice in order to amplify success margins within various member campaigns. Developed communication and journey outreach to members with team and oversaw the deployment of campaigns to the individual member audience.

- Participated as member channel representative for platform migration efforts.
- Peer development facilitator with regard to training and ramp-up with continued team training efforts for both onsite and offshore developers
- Oversaw a channel of ~4.7M active/subscribed records
- Continued support of complex and dynamic email campaign builds.

#### State Auto Insurance Company

March 2000 - January 2017

### **Digital Communication Specialist Sr.**

**April 2015 - January 2017** 

Lifecycle management to create, update, and maintain existing Ektron, ASP, JavaScript websites and portals using HTML, CSS, and SQL. Partnered for development and implementation of Drupal, PHP, MySQL, and Ektron content management systems for new websites and portals. Local internal training lead for new faster, more reliable, policy quoting system.

- Championed daily stand-ups, keeping team on target and focusing involved project groups.
- Created dynamic personalized email and web content using the Salesforce Marketing Cloud, identifying and targeting audiences and allowing metrics collection for open rates, and receptiveness via A/B testing.
- Provided frontline support on special projects, detecting areas of improvement in software solutions and processes.

#### **Digital Communication Specialist II**

**April 2013 – April 2015** 

Sole responsibility for portal content publications, creation and distribution of templates, guidelines for targeted email communication, and disaster recovery communications. Onboard and mentor associates for brand standards, culture, voice and tone of digital and print communications. Created and maintained a knowledge base of procedures for publication of digital content for business continuity. Managed subscriber lists and groups in the Salesforce Marketing Cloud, for the publication of multiple internal newsletters.

- Collaborated with third party companies and internal stakeholders for the creation of new brand guidelines, standardizing styling using CSS of existing web interfaces for 'AgentSite', a portal allowing independent agencies to write business with State Auto.
- Provided instructional material to offshore developers and other associates, ensuring a consistent user experience.
- Evangelized, created and launched OneSource4U, a bi-weekly internal newsletter, and Marketing Portal updates, a quarterly notification of brochures and materials available for agents and insureds.

# **Eva Walls**

Indianapolis, Indiana 46217 https://www.linkedin.com/in/eva-walls 317-507-3845 EvaWalls@gmail.com

## **Web Designer II**

## October 2009 - April 2013

Developed 'Social Agent' microsite with Social Media Director to establish resources, content library, and training materials in a central location, utilizing RSS, twitter feeds and content management procedures. Created and put into action branding for internal and external communications and websites.

• Supported intranet web authors with training and guidance of new content management system, while maintaining existing intranet and internet websites and portals.

### Web Designer I

## **April 2005 – October 2009**

Provided break/fix internal and external user support for ecommerce portals on emergency on-call basis

- Led and managed production of content updates to ensure that publications were sent to agency audiences
- Completed first redesign of agency portal; including a personalized experience by applying user segmentation

### **Work Breakdown**

Content Publication	Maintenance and	Research and Design	Training and Mentoring
40%	Support	20%	10%
	30%		

#### **Education and Certification**

Eleven Fifty Academy - Web Development
Indiana Resident Producer Individual - Property and Casualty
Associate in General Insurance, AICPCU
Social Media Certification, State Auto Insurance Company
ExactTarget Certificate in Content Creation, ExactTarget
Associate in Insurance Services, AICPCU
Indiana University Purdue University at Indianapolis, Herron School of Art

2020 - Present 2017 2016

#### Skills and Technical Knowledge

Agile Scrum Transformation Google Analytics Redgate Data Compare Adobe CS6 - Photoshop SQL Server Management Studio Jira Heat Adobe Acrobat XI Pro 2008 R2 ServiceNow Salesforce Marketing Cloud Beyond Compare Microsoft Office Marketing Cloud AMPscript SharePoint 2010 Microsoft Visual Studio HTML, CSS, ASP, SQL Drupal 7 Ektron 7.66 G Suite Redgate Compare

#### **Special and Volunteer Interests:**

Boy Scouts of America: Crossroads of America; Pathfinders; Troop 564
Boy Scouts of America: Crossroads of America; Pathfinders; Troop 183
Boy Scouts of America: Crossroads of America; Pathfinders; Pack 183
Private International Mother's Group

March 2018 – Present
February 2017 – March 2018
February 2016 – February 2017
July 2005 – Present

• Developer and administrator for online mother's group; diversity, camaraderie, support, and empowerment provided through cross channel communications.